Jotaro!
Do you hear what you're saying right now?!
Of course I do.
Finally starting to lose
your hearing, old man.
Obviously, I just told him my next pitch.
I'm gonna win with a
high outside fastball.
But, Jotaro, you...
Will you believe me?
Or will you doubt me instead?
Hmph.
Not too bright, are you?
My stand peers into
your soul the same way a
thermal imager detects
an object's radiation.
Say what you will, your soul cannot lie.
Regardless of what it is,
by analyzing your soul I can see the
answer to any yes or no question.
Right or left, high or
low, outside or inside,
fastball or curveball, my
stand's perception is infallible.
It's not to be the only
one who is the only
one who is the one who
is the one
who
has been.
I'm still in love with
the power of the dragon.
I'm not sure how many men are looking.
I'm not still looking for
the chance to reach the place.
I'm still looking for the
moment when I'm in a war.
I'm going to be able to shoot
the sword of the dragon!
Stop, it's now.
What was the story of the
story that's been taken?
I'll be the next time.
I'll be the end of the day.
I'll be the next time. The Crusaders.
The last page.
I'll be the last one.
End of the world.
The last one.
I'll be the last one.
Ola Ola Ola Ola!
Will your pitch be a
high outside fastball?
Yes or no?
Well, Chotaro's telling
the truth after all.
He's really going to pitch
a high outside fastball.
What's he up to?
It's true that he beat
my brother by bluffing,
but he's a fool if he thinks the
same tired tactic will work with me.
Here it comes.
For your sake,
I hope you haven't forgotten that you'll
lose the game if you fall 11 runs behind.
Was that a curve impossible I thought
he was going for a high outside fastball
He hits but it's a grounder the
ball is thrown to first and out
There's just no way everything about
him said he was going to throw a
high outside fastball His soul can't
lie no one's can not a zen master not
even my brother and he's the world's
greatest Con man next up is another
what the hell He's telling the truth!
Jotaro, you have the goal to
cheat your way to victory?
He actually is cheating!
Hello inside forkball!
It's a flyball heading
for the pitcher! Out!
You must have cheated!
Admit it! You bastard!
You clearly tampered with the console!
He's telling the truth?
I know you're cheating me.
You have to be!
Would you just come clean already?
No response. Damn it! That's right.
I only have use of my power if
I ask him a yes or no question.
Judging from your scared expression,
your power requires a yes or no question.
It's like your brother used to say.
This is just a dance of deception
where the loser cries first.
A dance, eh?
So this is nothing but a game to you?
How dare you?
Are you taking me for a fool?
Have you any idea who you're speaking to?
Jotaro, pitch the ball!
I'll figure out your little trick
and take your soul as my prize!
Alright.
Let's continue.
For my next pitch, I'll throw
a high outside fastball.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Once again, his soul says
he's telling the truth.
He's really going to pitch
a high outside fastball.
I've had about as much
of this as I can take.
This ends now.
I'll figure out how you're cheating
if it's the last thing I do.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
So, Jyotaro hasn't changed his mind.
He's still dead set on
throwing that infernal pitch!
It's coming!
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
So far, it's still a fastball,
and his soul is saying yes!
It changed direction!
A forkball!
What?!
It's a different pitch now!
Yes, yes, yes!
Ouch!
That's three outs! Change!
I don't get it.
Why can't I figure out how he's cheating?
Jotaro's soul kept saying
he'd throw a fastball,
but at the last second it
curved into a forkball.
This doesn't make any sense.
How?
How is this wretch deceiving me?
You're going to lose this game, Darby.
Shut your mouth! Come on.
Tell me why you removed your stupid hat.
I'm more perceptive than
you think I know you've
been cheating ever since
you took it off now move.
I want to check your
station and controller
There's nothing here damn you.
How did you do it?
It must have something to
do with that hat of yours.
Isn't that right?
No, no, no, no
There must be evidence
around here somewhere!
You're using Star Platinum
to cheat, aren't you?
No, no, no, no!
Just admit it!
You're doing something!
Dammit! Dammit!
I can clearly read Jotaro's thoughts!
Which means my stand's power
is still working as it should!
So how can his mind say one
thing but his body do another?
Hey, Jotaro, are you seeing this?
Looks like he's losing his youthful glow.
He definitely doesn't look
like a guy in his 20s anymore.
Darby, it's your turn to pitch, so hurry.
We don't have all day.
It's 4 to 3.
With only a one-point difference,
I might still have a chance.
I am a video game genius.
I can't lose.
I've won every game I've ever played.
I'm invincible.
A video game expert is an expert at life.
Do you think you can shake
my confidence so easily?
Look at that! Another home run!
That's another run for the Jaguars, folks!
It's five to three.
It can't be!
I accidentally released his
soul from the doll! Look!
His soul has returned to his body!
He's regaining consciousness!
No! I didn't!
I never once admitted defeat!
It was an accident!
I didn't mean to release
his soul from the doll!
But the thing is, you
did release his soul.
You know what that means.
Your soul admitted defeat
and it's game over.
Huh? Hold on. This...
is Joseph's stand?
It was wrapped around the
controller the entire time!
Huh? Whoops.
I guess I forgot to put this away.
How could something so stupid...
No.
You mean it was Joseph?
He was the cheater all along? Damn it.
Jotaro is telling the truth.
He really wasn't controlling it.
It was you, Joseph Joestar!
too bad you're not your
brother because if you
were you would have
figured it out a long time
ago by the way old man
you're pretty clever
i didn't expect you to catch on to my idea
as quickly as you did
well of course i did my
boy i can read you like a book you are my
grandson after all now
up and at him cock you in
joseph was controlling things from behind
before i forget what to
do with you you button
-mashing jerk oh shit
please mercy i beg you
i've already given you
back cock you in seoul
haven't i it's like
they say no harm no foul
we're good right right
right you want to know
whether i'll forgive
you why don't Why don't
you just do what you do
best and read my mind?
Answer this.
Will I hit you with my right fist
or decide to deck you with my left?
I'd love to know.
Well, since you're asking,
you'll use your right one?
No, no, no, no, no!
Then your left?
You're not gonna use both, are you?
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
Yes!
Are you gonna do the Aurora thing?
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, my God.
Darby Younger, out of commission!
How about that?
We broke through some sort of wall.
That's our ticket out of here.
Jotaro! Cock you in!
Good grief.
Forgive me for disturbing you.
But, Your Excellence, as
I'm sure you're aware,
Joestar and his comrades have
just infiltrated the manor.
Regrettably, I must also inform
you that Darby has been defeated.
Oh, but Darby was a genius.
How could one as gifted as Darby fail me?
Come, I'd like to hear your thoughts.
You may enter Cool Ice.
As you wish.
Always remember this.
Whatever the obstacle,
whatever the danger,
the Joestars are prepared to sacrifice
their lives in order to save their family.
Kakyoin and the other two.
What were their names again?
Ah, yes.
I believe it's Avdol and Polnareff.
They're willing to surrender their lives
for the eradication of yours truly.
They believe fleeing from me is somehow
the same as running from themselves.
Fools, one and all.
Nonetheless, the fools find
strength in this misguided belief.
Darby swore his undying loyalty.
But unfortunately, he was not
prepared to actually die on my behalf.
Which is why, at the edge of glory,
victory slipped through his fingers.
For the rest of eternity,
Darby will remain in ignorance.
Ice, have a look at the scar on my neck.
Jonathan Joestar's body
is still rejecting me,
but I need the blood of one more soul
before this body truly becomes mine.
And once that happens,
the wound will heal.
Ice, will you offer me the crimson
vigor coursing through your veins?
Yes, it'd be an honor.
What is mine is yours.
Ah, you beheaded yourself.
Most splendid.
What cool ice.
I cannot accept the blood
of such a loyal servant.
My wound shall be healed, but it
will be with the blood of another.
For now, you must live.
So awaken and be reborn.
Your steadfast resolve shall secure
your victory over those who'd oppose me.
I shall not fail you, my lord.
No weapon can surpass one's own body.
You are ready, Kulice.
Now go and attend to our unwanted guests.
I swear, Lord Dio, I
will not let you down.
You have my word.
I'll destroy them all.
Well, I sincerely hope that for your sake,
your next victim into the void will be
one of the Joestars and not my boudoir.
The ten minutes he gave us are up.
I know that Mr.
Joestar ordered us to
set the mansion on fire.
But I say we go.
We have to find them. Agreed.
Polnareff, before we proceed,
there's something I need to tell you.
Listen well.
If you lose your way, get injured, or
can't go on, I won't come to your rescue.
you.
Make sure you understand that.
Same for you, Iggy.
I know that might sound cruel,
but remember the reason we're here
is to defeat Dio once and for all.
And of course, the same rules
must apply to me as well.
If I'm injured or separated from
you, you have to promise you
won't attempt to save me.
Above all else, you must
think of your own safety.
We can't let ourselves get killed
trying to save one another.
There's too much at stake.
Oui, that's how it goes then.
If we get out of this alive, you're
treating me to one hell of a meal.
I'll treat you both.
Alright, let's go!
Do your thing, Silver Chariot!
Hey, Avdol, what do we do now?
This place looks like it goes on forever.
I know Mr.
Joestar told us to set
the mansion on fire,
but setting this immense labyrinth ablaze
would end up putting us all in danger.
So instead...
Magicians Red!
These flames detect life forms.
They can sense anything alive,
detecting even cutaneous
respiration and minute movements.
These flames can also sense a stand's
energy, so we'll let them lead the way.
Any particular reason
there are six flames?
There's one for each direction,
as well as for above and below.
If there is anything
hidden within 15 meters,
regardless of its size, the flame will
detect its presence and alert us immediately.
Mr.
Joestar and the others
were pulled below us.
Let's head down.
The flames are picking up on something.
Apparently it's in
front of us to the left!
What is...
What the hell?
Who's this guy supposed to be?
Look, do you see what's
happening, Polnareff?
Huh?
The maze!
It's totally disappeared!
I'm willing to bet the power
of this man stand created the
illusion of the maze it dissipated
as soon as Iggy slashed him.
His name Billy Jean his
fate instant defeat.
The mansion is back to normal now.
So we averted at least
one potential crisis and
the flames don't seem to
be sensing any danger?
The flames don't sense a thing.
And Iggy hasn't picked
up on anything either.
My god!
What is that abomination?
Impossible!
Neither my flames nor Iggy could sense it!
Where did it come from?
Polnareff, Iggy, you have
to get out of here now!
Hey!
Where are you, Avdol? The hell?
What was that thing? Where did it...
No, it can't be.
Whose arms are…
Hey, Avdol, where did you go?
Avdol, where are you?
Avdol, come out, Avdol!
What the hell is that thing?
Where did it come from?
Weren't Avdol's flames supposed
to be able to sense anything?
Hey, Iggy!
Couldn't your nose pick up on this thing?
Answer me!
Avdol, where are you?
Where the hell'd you go?
Avdol.
Has been reduced to nothingness.
Beyond my jaws lies an
endless void a dark dimension
which harbors things even
I do not fully comprehend.
Your ally is dead but fret
not as you will soon join him.
You were arrogant enough to
believe you could defeat Lord Dio.
Therefore you must be punished.
One by one,
each of you shall fall in
line as I scatter your atomic
fragments across the deepest
recesses of the Void.
No, you're lying.
It's impossible.
There's no way you killed Abzal.
How dare you lie to me!
Thank you.